{
	"hues": [
		{"question": "#ff0000",
		 "answer": "0"},

		{"question": "#ff8800",
		 "answer": "1"},

		{"question": "#ffff00",
		 "answer": "2"},

		{"question": "#80ff00",
		 "answer": "3"},

		{"question": "#00ff00",
		 "answer": "4"},

		{"question": "#00ff80",
		 "answer": "5"},

		{"question": "#00ffff",
		 "answer": "6"},

		{"question": "#0080ff",
		 "answer": "7"},

		{"question": "#0000ff",
		 "answer": "8"},

		{"question": "#8000ff",
		 "answer": "9"},

		{"question": "#ff00ff",
		 "answer": "10"},

		{"question": "#ff0080",
		 "answer": "11"}
	]
}
